Sarka Sevcikova

- www.sarkasevcikova.com
- in linkedin.com/in/sarkasevcikova



I am experienced in content development and web design with a proven track record of success in digital accessibility and marketing automation. Certified Professional Scrum Master. I am a fast learner with an eye for detail who enjoys working in international teams.

EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MANAGER

Coral Travel | 11/2022-ongoing

- Collaborating with multinational teams to plan, localize, and design a B2B platform for travel agencies
- Creating landing pages, forms, and workflows on an automation platform, content management, and reporting

Utilizing Jira, Asana, proprietary CMS, SALESmanago automation platform, Google Analytics

CLIENT SERVICES MANAGER / MARKETING COORDINATOR FOR MICROSOFT

Wunderman Thompson, remote | 11/2020-04/2022

- Cooperated with Microsoft stakeholders to organize, create, plan, and execute digital campaigns for Microsoft Azure in the CEE Area. It primarily included web development and email marketing.
- Created accessibility and web development guidelines based on WCAG for the team and external agencies

Used Dynamics 365, MS Clarity UX Tool, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe Analytics, Power BI.

TECHNICAL WRITER

Rockwell Automation, remote | 01/2020-10/2020

- Collaborated with multiple cross-functional teams to design and improve the technical documentation, developed tutorials, user friendly how-to articles, and diagrams
- Redesigned the documentation and the internal website based on user research and guidelines

Utilized agile tools like Jira and Confluence, along with Adobe XD, Markdown, Wordpress, Draw.io diagramming tool, and git version-control system

DIGITAL SERVICE DELIVERY PLANNER FOR MICROSOFT

Wunderman Thompson | 12/2018–12/2019

 Coordinated the website creation process and provided consultations to stakeholders on web design, accessibility, tools, and processes

- Responsibility for the output of the Digital Team (10+ people).
- Completed website accessibility assessments and concluded final evaluations

Mostly used ServiceNow, Dynamics 365, proprietary CMS, HTML5, CSS3, JS, and Adobe Photoshop.

DIGITAL SPECIALIST / CODER

Wunderman Thompson | 09/2017–12/2018

- Developed and maintained responsive and accessible Microsoft corporate websites, HTML emails and templates
- Ensured compliance with Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG), Quality Assurance
- Redesigned websites following brand guidelines and WCAG

Used Bootstrap/ Microsoft Web Framework, WordPress, proprietary CMS (SiteMuse/ MSCOM CMS, RedTiger CMS), HTML5, CSS3, JS, Salesforce Marketing Cloud, Litmus Email Testing Tool, and Adobe Photoshop

WEB CONTENT EDITOR

Czech Radio | 06/2019–11/2016

- Content creation and publishing lifestyle articles for <u>Radiozurnal.cz</u> (I wrote 2000+ articles)
- Studio photography, photo manipulation, audio editing for podcast

TOOLS

- Multimedia: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD, Sound Forge Audio Studio, Audacity
- **Web technologies**: HTML5, CSS, basics of JS, Web Content Accessibility Guidelines, Litmus Email Testing Tool, Salesforce Marketing Cloud, SALESmanago
- Wordpress, comprehensive overview of publishing platforms and workflows
- Analytics tools: Google Analytics, Clarity UX Tool
- Project management tools: ServiceNow, Dynamics 365, Jira, Confluence, Asana

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

Professional Scrum Master issued by Scrum.org in 2021

acquired skills: the Scrum framework, the Scrum Master role, how to apply Scrum

Google UX Design issued Coursera/ Google in 2022

acquired skills: the foundations of UX design, wireframing, prototyping, and testing

Higher professional degree in Economics and Marketing

LANGUAGES

English professional proficiency

Swedish intermediate (B1/B2), Glossa Sweden school graduate

Czech native speaker